Anna: Hi there! I’m Anna and I live in Washington, D.C. Every day I learn more about this great city. People in Washington like to work out! Oh, hi, Pete. How’s it going?
Pete: Hi, Anna. It’s going great. How’s it going with you?
Anna: Things are awesome! Pete, I want to work out. Where is the gym?
Pete: The gym is across from the lounge. It’s next to the mailroom. Go that way.
Anna: Thanks, Pete!
Anna: Oh, Pete. This is not the gym.
Pete: That’s right, Anna. This is the mailroom.
Anna: The gym is across from … what?
Pete: The gym is across from the lounge.
Anna: Across from the lounge. Right. Thanks!
Anna: Pete! This is not the gym!
Pete: The gym is across from the lounge. It is behind the lobby.
Anna: Right. Right. See you.
Pete: See you, Anna!
Anna: See you.
Pete: See you, Anna.
Anna: Pete! Pete?
Pete: I want to work out too! Join me!
Anna: I’m good.